New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 4/19/02-10/19/02. (Box 19)
  - Capital District Labor-Religion Coalition Breakfast, NYSUT Latham, NY, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Cornell NYSSILR Advisory Council Ithaca, New York, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    Oct 18-19
- Meeting Files, 10/21/02-5/22-03. (Box 20)
  - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, Union Square Park, New York City, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Oct 28, 10:30am
  - Cornell Class, 34th Street, NYC Room - Sheraton, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Oct 28, 4:30pm
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Oct 31-Nov 2, 1 of 2
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, NY, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Oct 31-Nov 2, 2 of 2
  - Bruno Reception w/Cornell University Club, Albany, NY, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Nov 5, 5pm
  - Committee on New American Realities, Sofitel Lafyette Square, 806 15th Street, NW, Washington, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Nov 6-7, 2pm
  - State Workforce Investment Board, Crown Plaza, Albany, NY, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Nov 14, 10am
  - Cornell School of Industrial & Labor Relations Video Conference, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Nov 18, 2:55pm
  - CWA Stop the Layoffs! Rally Albany Labor Temple, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Nov 20, 6pm
  - NYSUT ED 12-14 Meeting Holiday Inn, Newburgh, NY, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Nov 21, 7pm
  - Alliance for Excellent Education AEE, 1101 Vermont Avenue, NW Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Nov 26, 9:30am
  - Pension Meeting, NYC Office, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Dec 3, 11am
  - State Federation Officers Conference, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Dec 6, 12pm
  - AFL-CIO Advancing the Alliance Meeting, G. Mean Conference Rm., AFL-CIO Headquarters, Washington DC, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Dec 19, 10am
  - IRRA Annual Meeting, Hyatt Regency Capitol Hill, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Jan 3-5
  - AFT Democracy Committee Meeting, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Jan 6, 11am
  - Advancing the Alliance Meeting, AFL-CIO Headquarters, Geo. Meany Room Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Jan 8, 10 am
  - Northeast Council, Condado Plaza, Puerto Rico, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Jan 9-15
  - John LaFalce Retirement Dinner, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Jan 31
  - Advancing the Alliance Mtg., AFL-CIO Headquarters, Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Jan 31, 10am
  - ARA Meeting w/ Ed Coyle Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Feb 5, 2:30pm
  - NAVE Advisory Panel Meeting, Capitol Holiday Inn, 550 C Street, SW Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Feb 6-7
  - NYSUT Board of Director's Mtg., 2003 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Feb 8, 11am
  - NYSARA Officer's Meeting 48 E. 21st Floor, NYC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    Feb 13, 10 am
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, Florida, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Feb 21-28
  - National Training Conf. for WIB Labor Representatives, Hilton Crystal City Hotel, National Airport, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    March 3
  - Cornell University Board of Directors Meeting, Ithaca, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    Mar 5-7
  - Workforce Development Meeting, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    Mar 12-13
  - WNY Retirees 10:30am Boody Meeting 2pm UAW Hall, Genesee Street, Buffalo, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Somos El Futuro Conference Legislative Breakfast, Crowne Plaza Hotel, 2nd Level, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - St. Pat Parade, 1:20p Assemble E 46th, bet Madison & Vanderbilt, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    Mar 17
  - AFT Democracy Committee Meeting, AFT, 55 New Jersey Avenue, NW, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Mar 19, 11am
  - State Workforce Investment Board Four Points Hotel, 120 Main Street East, Rochester, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    Mar 20, 10am
  - NYATEP Adv. Bd., Four Points Hotel, 120 Main Street E, Rochester, New York, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Mar 20, 12pm
  - Meeting with Jean Stevens, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    April 1, 2pm
  - NYSUT RA, Hilton Washington Hotel, 1919 CT Avenue, NW, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    April 3-5
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Luncheon, The Grand Hyatt Hotel, Park Ave & Grand Central Sta., NYC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    April 8, 12pm
  - AFL-CIO/UALE Educ. Conf. Sheraton Bal Harbour Resort, Bal Harbour, FL, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    April 9-12
  - PSC Press Conference Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    April 14
  - Workforce Investment Act Conference, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - committee on New American Realities, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace Conference Ctr. 1779 Mass. Ave, NW, Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    April 30-May 1
  - AFT Comm on Career & Technical Education, AFT National Office, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    April 30-May 2
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council The Greenbrier, W Virginia, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - NYSUT;s March for Public Education, Empire State Plaza, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    May 3, 1pm
  - NAVE, US Dept of Education, 400 Maryland Avenue, SW., Rm. 1W105-108, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Congressional Breakfast, Rayburn HOB, Room 2325 Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    May 7, 8am
  - AFT International Affairs Seminar, AFT Headquarters, 4th Floor Conference Room ,Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Troy Area Labor Council Public Forum, K. Doyle Middle School, 1976 Burdett Ave, Troy, NY, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    May 13, 6:30pm
  - Equipped for the Future National Policy Group, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Dinner with R. Trumka Bello Restaurant, 863 9th Avenue, NYC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    May 16, 6:30pm
  - State Workforce Investment Board Meeting, Albany, Mariott, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Nat'l Research Center for Career & Tech Ed, Rm. B, Center for high Ed., One Dupont circle, Washington, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    May 20, 9am
  - CWE Board Meeting, Consortium 257 7th Avenue, 27th Floor, NYC, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    May 22, 11:30am
- Meeting Files, 6/3/03-11/12/03. (Box 21)
  - NYSARA Officers Meeting, 800 Troy Schenectady Road, Latham, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    June 3, 11am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting NYSUT Headquarters, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    May 27-30
  - Union ChildCare Coalition Board Meeting, NYC CLC, 3rd Floor Boardroom, 31 W 15th Street, NYC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    June 19, 8:30am
  - NYARA Officer Meeting NYSUT Headquarters, Latham, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    June 23, 11am
  - AFL-CIO Work & Family Conference, Fairmont, Hotel Chicago, IL, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    June 26
  - American Labor Studies Committee Meeting - NYS AFL-CIO, 100 South Swan Street, Albany, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Tuesday July 1, 11am
  - ALSC Board Meeting @ NYS AFL-CIO, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    July 1, 11am
  - AFT Executive Council, Jefferson Room, Concourse Level, Hilton Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    July 9, 9:30am
  - National Labor in the Schools Symposium, Washington Hilton, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    July 9-10, 8:30am
  - NSSB Dinner with Jaime Houghton, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    July 17, 6pm
  - NYSARA Board Meeting, NYC CLC, 31 W 15th Street, 3rd Fl Conf Room New York City, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    July 28, 11am
  - NYATEP Meeting, 111 Pine Street, Albany, New York, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Aug 6, 10am
  - Meeting with Denis & Barry Feinstein CWE offices, NYC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Aug 7
  - ALSC Teacher Advisory Committee Meeting, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY 12210, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Aug 27, 10:30am
  - Alliance for Retired Americans National Legislative Conference Hilton Washington & Towers, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Sept 3- 5
  - ILR Advisory Council, Ithaca, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Sept 12-13
  - New York State Nurses Assoc. Delegate Assembly, 11 Cornell road, Latham, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Sept 17, 10:45am
  - State Workforce Investment Board, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    sept 17
  - Senator Jim Alesi Annual golf Tournament, Midvale Golf & Cty Club Penfield, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - FPI Budget Balancing & Strategies Meeting, Emmanuel Baptist Church, 275 State Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - NY Labor History Assoc annual Meeting UFT, 60 Broadway, Conf Ctr A: Main Floor, NYC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Sept 25, 6:15pm
  - CWA/NABET Local 21 Press conference, Channel 13 News Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    Sept 29, 12pm
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, Washington Park, H Johnson Blvd & State Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    Sept 30, 4:30pm
  - Fiscal Policy Institute Policy Advisory Board, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    Oct 1, 10:30am
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, Flushing Meadows Park, Queens, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    Oct 4, 11am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Hyatt Regency, 400 New Jersey Ave, NW Washington DC, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    Oct 8-9
  - Workforce Training & Educ Coordinating Bd's 3rd Statewide Conference, Coast Wenatchee Ctr. Hotel, Wenatchee, VA, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - AFT Democracy Committee AFT Executive Council Washington Court Hotel, 525 NJ Ave, Washington DC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    Oct 8, 8am, 1 of 2
  - AFT Democracy Committee AFT Executive Council, Washington Court Hotel, 525 NJ Ave., Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    Oct 8, 8am, 2 of 2
  - S Boehlert Fundraiser, Otesaga Hotel, Cooperstown, NY, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    Oct 10, 7:30pm
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees, Ithaca, New York Room - Statler Hotel, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    Oct 16-18
  - Northeast council, AFL-CIO Cape May, New Jersey, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    Oct 13-16
  - Bishop Class, Cornell University, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Tennessee Employment Relations Research Association, Arnold Lakeside Center, Arnold air Force Base, TN, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    Oct 29- 31
  - SWIB Meeting, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - OECD/NCAL International Roundtable, Hilton Inn @ Penn, Philadelphia, PA, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    Nov 2-14
- Meeting Files, 11/19/03-4/26/04. (Box 22)
  - Troy Historic Society Meeting, 57 Second Street, Troy, NY, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Nov 19, 10am
  - Working For American Inst. 2003 National Conference, Hyatt Regency Milwaukee, WI (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Nov 9-12
  - Meeting with T Riley, L Cutler, J Bloom, C. Garnder & PFC, CB Driscolls, Newburgh, NY, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Nov 24, 6:30pm
  - Cornell 1st Annual Labor Leaders Roundtable, Statler Hotel, Ithaca, NY Nov 21, 12pm, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Empire State Advantage, NYS Business council, Washington Avenue, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Nov 24, 10:30a-3p
  - Parrot/Fleron Meeting, 50 Broadway, New York, NY, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - IBT 2003 Annual Skills for Tomorrow Meeting, Washington Court Hotel, Washington, DC (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Jan 4-5
  - Cornell University Union Leadership Series Workshop, 16E 34th Street, 4th Floor, NY, NY, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Shanker Institute Washington, DC, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    Dec 16, 9:30am
  - IRRA 56th annual Meeting Holiday Inn On The Bay, San Diego, CA, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Condado Plaza Hotel, San Juan, PR, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Jan 8-13
  - Labor Resumes, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - CWE Artisan Baking Center 36-36 37th Street, LIC, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    Jan 14, 12pm
  - State Workforce Investment Board Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Jan 15, 1pm
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Westin Diplomat Resort, Hollywood FL, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Jan 21-24
  - NYSARA Board of Directors SEIU Office, New York City, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Jan 26, 1pm
  - NYSARA Board Meeting, 1199, 330 W. 42nd Street, New York City, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - UUP Winter Delegate Assembly Desmond hotel, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Jan 30, 7:30pm
  - Albert Shaker Institute Corporate Members Meeting, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Feb 5
  - AFT Executive Council and PPC Meetings Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel, Miami, FL, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Feb 3-6
  - AFL-CIO General Board Meeting, AFL-CIO Headquarters, Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Feb 19
  - Alliance for Retired Americans Executive Board Meeting, Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel, Bal Harbour, FL, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    Mar 8, 1pm
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, Sheraton Bal Harbour Hotel 9701 Collins Avenue, Bal Harbour, FL, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    Mar 9- 11
  - Child Care Lobby Day Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    Mar 16, 10:30am
  - Conference Call w/ Commissioner Mills, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    Mar 17, 4:30pm
  - Sons of St Patrick's Dinner Sheraton, NYC, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - NYSUT RA, New York Hilton, New York, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    Mar 25-27
  - Press conference on World Trade Centre, City Hall, New York city, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    Mar 29, 12pm
  - Cornell Univ. Advisory council Mtg. & Groat Award, Roosevelt Hotel, NYC, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    April 1, 2:30pm
  - Meeting w/ David Brooks Washington DC, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    April 8
  - NYSARA, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    April 21
  - New Alliance - Phase 2, Quality Inn, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    April 23-24, 1pm, 1 of 2
  - New Alliance - Phase 2, Quality Inn, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    April 23-24, 2 of 2
  - Hispanic & Puerto Rican Labor Caucus, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    April 24
  - Labor religion, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Meeting Files, 5/1/04-1/6/05. (Box 23)
  - Hudson Mohawk May Day, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Northeast Council, AFL-CIO Meeting, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    May 3-4
  - NE AFL-CIO Council, Otesage Hotel Cooperstown, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    May 2-4
  - The Empire State Advantage Excellence @ Work, Desmond Hotel, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    May 4-5, 2:30p/8a
  - SWIB Committee Chairs Conference Call, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    May 6, 8:30am
  - C.O.P.E. Meeting - New York State AFL-CIO, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - White-Smith Meeting at Mullany House, Troy, New York, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    May 10, 9:15am
  - CWE Board Meeting 275 7th Avenue, New York City, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    May 13, 10 am
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Holiday Inn Express, Western Ave Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    May 13, 1pm
  - NYSARA NYSUT Headquarters, Latham, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    May 18, 11am
  - AFT CTE Committee Meeting, Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    May 13-15, 4pm
  - Building Workforce Partnerships conference, Roosevelt Hotel, NYC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    May 19-21
  - AFT Executive Council & PPC Mtgs. UFT, 50 Broadway, NYC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    May 24-27
  - NYS AFL-CIO Exec. Committee & Council Meeting, crown Plaza, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    June 2, 11am
  - National ARA Meeting Pittsburgh, PA, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    June 6-7
  - Albert Shanker Institute, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Feb -May 1 of 2
  - Albert shankar Institute, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Feb - May 2 of 2
  - Hudson-Mohawk Urban Cultural Park commission, Riverspark Visitor Center, 251 River Street, Troy, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    June 25, 9am
  - 4th World Congress of education international, Porto Alegre, Brazil, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    July 22-26
  - AFT Convention, Washington Convention Center, Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    July 13-15
  - Moree Conference Call, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    July 12, 11am
  - Binghamton (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Sept 2
  - Labor Day Rally Press Kit NYC CLC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - United Way of NYS (Box 23, Folder 24)
    Sept 10
  - Fundraiser for Dennis Tracey, Diana's Restaurant, 607 Route 207 New Windsor, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    Aug 19, 4:30pm
  - Bruno Luncheon, Sheraton Hotel, NYC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Sept 2, 12:30pm
  - Cornell Univ. Board of Trustees Retreat, Doral Arrowwood, Rye Brook, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    Sept 9-10
  - Hall of Fame, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    sept 21-22
  - Labor Roundtable, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    sept 23
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Hilton Garden Inn @ Alb Airport 800 Albany-Shaker Road, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    Sept 23, 1pm
  - Retirement Salute to Sonny Hall Sheraton Towers, NYC, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    Oct 9, 6pm
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Hyatt Regency, Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Advisory Council Meeting, Ithaca, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    Oct 15-16
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    Oct 13-15
  - Opening Newly Renovated ILR Conference Center, Cornell University, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - 2004 NYSUT BOCES Leadership Conference Desmond Hotel Albany, NY (Box 23, Folder 36)
    Oct 22
  - Albany ALF Meeting 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    Oct 23, 1pm
  - Albany ALF Meeting 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    Oct 27, 1pm 2 of 2
  - CWA Local 1104 SUNY Campus Center Sm. Fountain Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    Oct 28, 11am
  - CD Union Label & Service Trades Council Michael' Banquet House Latham, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - NRCCTE Advisory Team Meeting Jury's Washington Hotel, Washington DC, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Nov 4-5
  - Washington State's Leadership Conference, Tacoma, WA, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    Nov 9-10
  - OSU NAVE Webcast OSU, 1900 Kenny Road, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Hilton Garden Inn at the Albany Airport, 800 Albany-Shaker Road, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    Nov 18, 1pm
  - 84th NCSS Annual Conference, Baltimore Convention Center, Baltimore, MD, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    Nov 19-21
  - Workers Rights Board, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    December 10, 2004.
  - December Regents Meeting, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    Dec 16-17
  - Mullany House & Park Planning Group Meeting, 100 S Swan Street, Albany, NY, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    Dec 20, 10am
  - Work Readiness Credential Meeting Wegman's, Pittsford, NY, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    Jan 4, 12pm
  - NE council Meeting San Juan, Puerto Rico, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    Jan 6-12
- Meeting Files, 1/13/05-5/31/05. (Box 24)
  - SWIB Meeting, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Trustee Dinner, Mandarin Oriental, 80 Columbus Circle @ 60th Street 35th Floor NYC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Jan 21, 7pm
  - Budget Briefing, 711-A LOB Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - IRRA Dinner, Desmond Hotel, 660 Albany-Shaker Road, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Jan 25, 6pm
  - GMNY Social Studies Conference NY Marriott & Brooklyn Bridge Brooklyn, NY 11201, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Jan 29, 7:30am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Disney Boardwalk Resort, Orlando, FL, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Jan 31, 9am
  - Regents Meeting, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Feb 7, 10:30am
  - NRCCTE Advisory Council Meeting, Jury's Washington Hotel, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Feb 8, 8:30am
  - Mullany House & Park Planning Committee, Peebles Island, Waterford, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Feb 15, 3pm
  - Peter Goodman Meeting, NYS AFL-CIO, 50 Broadway, NYC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Feb 16, 1pm
  - D Stock and 1 Stop, Dunkirk, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Feb 18
  - Empire State Advantage Board Meeting, Call In, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Feb 24, 1pm
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, Bally's Las Vegas, NV, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Mar 1-3
  - Capital District ALF Meeting, Labor Temple, 890 Third street, Albany, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Mar 5, 9am
  - NYSARA Board of Directors Meeting, CLC in NYC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Mar 7, 10:30am
  - University of Oslo Students New York City, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Mar 9
  - NYC Dept. of Education w/Michele Cahill, 52 Chamber Street, City Hall Park, 3rd Floor Conference Room, NYC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - NYSCSS/NYS4A Annual Convention, Saratoga Springs, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Hudson Valley ALF, Laborers Hall, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Mar 12, 8:30am
  - Friendly Sons of Saint Patrick Sheraton NY Hotel & Towers, New York, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Mar 17, 6:15pm
  - NYSSILR Advisory Council Meeting & GrOAT Award Dinner, Grand Hyatt, NYC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Mar 31, 3pm
  - CD ALF Labor/Youth Partnership Initiative Youth Action Alliance, 155 Washington Ave, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    April 5, 6pm
  - Empire State Advantage Board Meeting, Conference Call, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    April 15, 10:30am
  - NYS AFL-CIO Congressional Breakfast, RHOB, Room 2325, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    April 13, 8am
  - NYSUT RA, Hilton NY, 335 Ave of the Americas, NY, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    April 7-9
  - Somos Futuro Conference, Crowne Plaza Hotel, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    April 15, 6pm, April 16, 8pm
  - May Day 2005 Social Security Forum, Bush Memorial Ctr @ Russell Sage College, Troy, NY (Box 24, Folder 27)
    April 29, 7:30pm
  - NYSARA, Bi-Annual Convention, Albany Labor Temple, third Street, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    May 3, 10am
  - AFT CTE Committee Meeting Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    May 5-7, 2pm
  - Northeast Council Meeting, Hotel Viking, One Believe Avenue, Newport, RI, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    May 9-11
  - Hobart Retirement Dinner, Salvatore's Italian Gardens, 6461 Transit Road, Depew, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    May 12, 5:30pm
  - SWIB, Hilton Gardens @ Albany Airport, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    May 12, 10am
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting, Hyatt Regency, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    May 17-20
  - The Workforce Alliance Conference, Renaissance Washington Hotel, 999 Ninth Street, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    May 19
  - Draper & Bliven Meeting, Renss. Cty Historical society, 57 second Street, Troy, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    May 20, 10:30am
  - Baseball Hall of Fame Game Cooperstown, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - ESA Board Conference Call, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    May 26, 10:30am
  - CWE Board of Directors Meeting, 275 7th Avenue, New York, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    May 26, 10am
  - CWE Board of Directors, 275 7th Avenue, 18th Floor Board Room, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Mullany House Meeting, RCHS, 57 Second Street, Troy, NY, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    May 31, 10am
- Meeting Files, 6/27/05-11/2/05. (Box 25)
  - Workforce Development Institute Board, 24 Fourth Street, Troy, NY, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    June 27, 11am
  - QuEST, Hilton Washington Hotel, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    July 7-10
  - AFL-CIO Convention, Navy Pier, Chicago, IL, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    July 25-28
  - Alliance for Retired Americans Hilton Washington & Towers 1919 Connecticut Avenue, NW Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Sept 7-9
  - Senator Jim Alesi Annual All American Golf Tournament, Midvale Golf & Country Club, 2387 Baird Road, Penfield, NY, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Sept 19, 10:30am
  - M. Bahr Retirement dinner, Washington Hilton, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Sept 22, 6pm
  - Northeast Council meeting, Wyndham Baltimore Inner Harbor Hotel, Baltimore, MD, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Oct 3-5
  - NYS Workforce Investment Board Holiday Inn Turf, Wolf Road, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Oct 6, 10am
  - Consortium for Worker Education, 275 7th Avenue, 18th Floor Board room, New York, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Oct 12, 10am
  - Maritime Port Council Dinner, Sheraton NY & Towers, New York, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Oct 15